Welcome, everybody.
Welcome our our second session and.
We will actually, we will.
You can start.
Yeah guys,
please mute yourself if you didn't do so
or Eli will, Eli will help with this.
So we we started with recording. OK,
Yep.
so first of all again.
I hope everyone who wants joined already.
So I want to say that everything what we
are talking about here it's recorded and
processed by AI.
So and also the chat where we are talking
now also it recorded and processed by AI
LLM which are hosted in.
So if you have any issues with this so
just drop off please.
I don't want to convince you so like this
is this is about AI.
So that's why we use AI everywhere at
least right so.
Important for recording and for everyone
who is here and join to the chat.
All right, so.
We have two topics today,
so I promised to really set up the agent
for business analysis right in the way
how we're doing this and then I also want
to explain some details.
Like T theory part and the challenges and
things which should help you in future,
which to be honest I did not see
somewhere like properly described.
Probably it is,
but I don't like to read theories or you
relate to practice.
So from what do you want to start?
Like really set up this business analyst
agent in JIRA right now or start from
small tier first and then we continue
with the agent.
Let's vote for let's say first set up the
agent without tier.
Or first.
OK.
Two hands. Cool.
And Tioure first and then agent.
One hand super active audition. OK, 7810.
Cool. OK, let's then start from theorem.
Theory will be about context.
Even today, like I thought,
I I saw in the chat LM rule.
So I say like really important message,
you need to prepare the context and
they'll say just connect MCP context 7,
MCPZ, MCPZ,
MCPZ and then every all magic will happen.
Um,
and I really want to focus on this part.
Because I hear many times words like LMS,
LMS does not do what what we expect,
what we ask and etcetera. Yes,
so just for like context,
it's important to understand.
So today will be the quote.
So first of all.
If you raise your hands,
if you need to connect to to LLM,
you will go and connect for instance long
chain library,
set up long chain library and do some
prompts to the library.
Who will do like this? Raise your hands.
Or not blank chain,
maybe something else but some library.
OK, three hands, 5-7, OK,
maybe Spring AI or whatever,
or length for 4G or anything. Yeah, OK,
so cool.
And now let's change a bit things.
Who will you use?
Direct REST API to connect to LLM to send
some prompts.
24.
For hands that like 7-9. OK,
so now will be more I hope. OK, 5050.
I'm preference second part.
So when I started,
I started really with long chain and it
was two years ago I think or even more.
I started with these.
I I tried many things.
I I started to understand how context is
working, how how to write prompts,
like how technical it works.
So at and at some point I understood that
it is just URL.
And OST request.
There is no magic behind of it.
So and then I said OK,
why need like chain then?
So like because because everyone is using
it. So no, I don't like it.
So first of all,
like Python is not my technology first of
all. Yes. So that's why like it's.
First,
you know like it's not comfortable zone.
Yeah.
So then like if I can use just REST API,
why I need Python library?
So it's first question what I got. Sergey,
do you want to say something?
Or just.
OK, looks like just OK,
so let's let me show you something.
Again,
today will be more questions to you.
Do you see my screen?
Yeah.
Cool. So let's do not write in the chat,
but probably like or maybe a write,
Yep.
I don't know.
So let's think about context.
So first of all,
all all my connectors like it's my code,
it's my library.
I do not ask you to do same,
but I think most of you at the end.
Will have your own libraries because to
write the code connectors is pretty cheap.
So I have connectors to DL,
I have to Google,
to Ollama and other stuff.
So basically here just quickly to explain
it's DL connector which is what it does.
It's just like making HTTP request.
That's it. So there is some integrations,
there is some parcel of images,
blah blah blah,
but overall it just request to the API.
So that's why today I'm with VPN.
So like in case will be some issues with
connections, maybe it's because of VPN.
So and the L proxy for your model.
So it will be really useful for our
today's work.
I did write small integration test here
for TL integration and here I want to
show you something. So we have these.
Phrase.
Say hello in one word.
How many tokens we have here?
About 7.
H.
Seven. OK, 123 OK, seven. Who?
Who can tell something different?
Or or everyone thinks that it's 7.
8.
Just unmute yourself and say maybe in the
chat, but I don't.
Depends on the,
depends on the decanization logic.
So it could be more,
it should be more granular.
Yeah.
So there is no explicit answer I suppose.
Right dot can be token.
Blank may be token.
Pocket.
All right, it's it's already better.
So this is important to understand.
I I will show an example.
Let's use Gemini.
And run it.
So overall each models in API usually
they have kind of rest API like count.
If you send a prompt you can get the
count of tokens which is you're using.
Yes so but I'm from mobile world.
If I'm thinking like OK,
I have big prompt with request and I need
to perform the request twice,
first to count, 2nd to wait response.
I'm thinking oh something something is
wrong here. Yeah, I don't like it. OK,
we did use Gemini flash.
2.5 and there is 8.
8 tokens gemini 2.5.
I will not try but it will be the same
because it's same same family of the of
the models if I'm using this this one
Germany GPT 5 mini.
In output by the way it will be all time
different because some models are
thinking some models are no.
So that's why output it will be different.
But we interested in input you see total
tokens 89 even it did some like because
it did some thinking behind of it.
But prompt tokens is 14, yes,
so it's already twice more,
almost twice more.
So what's it means that tokens from
Google?
Cheaper than tokens from GPT 5.
Even they have some limitations,
like for instance,
Oh.
Google allows you million tokens to use,
let's say you know.
How is it cheaper?
How are they cheaper?
There are more than them, right?
At.
But does it have anything about cost in
it?
So for for instance,
if you need to process,
let's say 100 words.
In Google probably it will be 100 tokens,
but in GPT it's depending on uppercase,
lowercase, chair like some dots, quotes,
whatever. So it will be more expensive.
Mhm.
Yeah, so.
Uh, so more tokens. More tokens, you mean?
Mm-hmm. OK, OK, OK.
And more tokens you will use for the same
the same purposes.
So that's why like the cheapest tokens
it's like for Google.
But what is about entropic?
So we have like let let me write it here
was ape Google.
Threes than 14 GPT.
Let things that GPT 5 will give us the
same. Let's check on Tropic.
Personally like when I started at use I I
did use GPT a lot so but in post NL we do
have entropic models.
So that's why I really did start to to
think how entropics really can calculate
this. To be honest there is no logic.
I don't know still how to calculate
locally tokens for entropic,
so we have from tokens 16.
D. I
So even model allows you to use use
million tokens.
You still need to understand what tokens
mean. Yeah,
so because sometimes you really can put
your prompt to to like and request to to
to one big message,
send it and it will be 100.
1000 tokens,
but in other case it will be 200 and then
like even model allows you to use more.
It does not make sense because like
counting is different.
This is important to understand.
So when you're building a context,
but let's let's do more experiments like.
With Claude, Yeah.
So my preference is Claude because it's
really interesting to to to see how it's
changing. Yeah.
So let's imagine that you have Jason.
So now we have 16 tokens here. Yeah, but.
Let's think that we will have message, OK?
Message.
Let's do something like this.
It was 16. Let's run it again.
OK, I got closing bracket,
but for LLM it does not make sense.
But overall let's see 1919 I I find it's
the closing bracket.
Let's let's just rerun it.
Let's see,
it will be still 19 or it will be 20.
It's already 20.
Just one bracket and it is already 20.
Interesting.
And now start to think about all your MCP
tools.
About all your connectors.
Which you are using with these AI LLMS.
All of them or I don't know.
For almost all of them,
95% are using Jason's.
And that means that you just, you know,
like born tokens probably for nothing.
If you use it straightforward,
let me show another example.
Let's you take real Jira ticket.
I need to have here already tracker
client for instance perform ticket.
I did develop connectors to Microsoft
Teams.
So let me.
Use this ticket number.
It's GMC599 like this.
Usually if you use straightforward
connectors and if people could develop
this did not think about tokens.
Or economy of this.
In most cases you will get something like
it.
So the second parameter here it's
important, it is fields.
If I don't specify anything,
you'll get the ticket.
Let me just run it in debug.
All right, so you have a ticket.
And you have this you have expand self ID
fields, issues, avatars, the pain part,
this one. The pain is this.
The painting this. Do you need it?
I think no IDs.
Keys all of this it's it's really pain
and you see the interesting part is
description. What we really need,
what we really need as well.
We need also summaries,
summaries are probably fixed versions.
Sorry to interrupt,
but it seems we see only ADE but not the
There is also fields, custom fields.
Sorry,
but possible we do not see your side.
back window. You share only the.
Oh, OK. I'm sorry. Let me share my screen.
Mhm.
Thanks for the highlight by the way.
Talk more because it's should not be
wobble.
We can guess what? What is on your screen?
No problem here, but it's.
Yeah, OK, so ticket.
Now you see, right?
Yep, now it's visible.
Just another window.
Yep.
Yes, so this is Jason, which is.
It's really heavy for LLM,
but it's useless in most of the time.
So it's URLs. If you use URL,
it's a lot of tokens if you're thinking
in entropic words, let's say.
For others it's also a lot of tokens,
but it's not so visible as with entropic
models.
So because like for entropic it will be
like HTTPS probably 1 token,
another one more, one more,
then one more token.
If you have upper case it one more token,
lower case one more.
Token. It's really, really challenging,
right? If I just use this one,
let's try to build some font on top of it.
Let's me start debugging.
Over just to clarify the things, sorry,
are we making an assumption that the
Yeah, please.
talking price for different models are
the same?
Same.
No token price.
That's what I want to say first of all.
So with me.
Yeah,
the token price is different and this is
important to understand that like if I
see Antropic now has one million tokens
window.
I'm thinking OK,
probably I need to divide on 2.
I guess, well,
I guess we need to distinguish the two
Depending on the tasks.
things. One of them is price in tokens.
How many tokens does it take for the same
text, right? So it's like tokens per text,
right? Tokens enumerator,
text in the denominator.
But another one is like dollars per token
and you need to multiply 2 to get the
Mm-hmm.
actual cost, right?
So I guess the question was about the
Yeah, that's also true. That's also true.
I I I'm not thinking now about really
second one.
price of the tokens because it's anyway
cheap.
Why I'm focusing now on this one just
also to show you.
Difference like you can just send plain
Jason's, yes like it probably will work,
but as soon as you send more and more and
more Jason's or Aries or whatever else,
it will cost more money and at some point
you'll face with tokens limit. Yeah,
so this is important.
And understand for the same task you can
do this properly or you can do this just
straightforward and you will get lower
quality because context window will be
full with some other information which is
not required for for for your task. Yeah,
give me a short summary.
Hold that ticket for instance.
We we can even do like business analysis,
but it's done already. So OK, we get it.
So let's run it just for counting
purposes and just to understand what
happens.
And think now, for instance,
about HTML pages.
When you read HTML pages as a text,
it's more expensive even than Jason's.
So like because it has more many brackets,
many other stuff, yeah. So by the way,
when I tried it, it was slower than now,
but let's just prompt tokens.
10,000.
Ticket 10,000 OK,
let's let's just show you like,
but we need summary and description.
So let's just highlight summary and
description. Nothing else.
And you see it's still that restaurant.
OK,
let let's just see what what is that out.
Sorry.
Prom tokens.
You see difference.
If you just ask model or MCP default one.
Written to your Jira data to work with
ease.
You will get these.
So like you will eat these 10K tokens by
default. In most of the use cases,
most of the people don't care about these
fields. Even to be honest,
like in delivery central,
when you connect systems to the metrics,
guys don't really think about fields to
to specify.
They just call let's say JQL many times
in DM tools what I'm using like and what
was behind of it many years ago all this
field it's even required.
So to parameters sorry to specify because
I know like if I'm working with Jira I
need to know which tools.
Which fields exactly I need to call.
So in in this one in JQL and other stuff.
So that's why I'm really specifying it
all the time.
So we we have this one but like 5K, yeah,
but it's still Jason.
So you see this contains some unlocks.
I think it should be.
Yeah.
Yes,
this one expand render fields again links
which we don't know,
don't need some text etc.
If I just do get title.
Laz.
Get description.
So this is a description of our ticket.
By the way, where where where I OK,
this one.
I need to hide the window opens at the
end.
From tokens.
This one.
As Jason and this just route.
So basically this one it's minimal what
you can achieve for this ticket.
So imagine situation I want to do to to
to have context based on the Jira.
For my agent,
if I do this straightforward.
With 10K tickets,
so I can put only 10 tickets.
Let's if you're sinking in conditions
100K tokens per request.
If I need to,
if I'm simplifying this in this way,
I already can put 20 tickets, right?
So then I started to think how to make it
more or less automatically. Yeah,
so that's why in in my tools.
I'm also explaining this about my tools
because my assumption that at some point
people who is developing such agents,
they will have something similar,
but you need to understand what is behind
of it.
Yeah,
so like not just I connected length chain
and I do use it somehow.
You you should understand like you don't
have length chain,
you need to write it from the beginning
for instance,
and you need to understand how that works
each step.
So this is my goal to share it to you.
So in in ticket in Jira ticket I do have
so it is a model in most of the objects
which are used by LLM.
I do have these two text method.
What it does.
So basically I did develop kind of format
like LM optimize Jason which is designed
specifically to to to reduce the size.
In most cases,
most of the cases it reduces the size.
But not all the time.
So there is can be some Jason's which can
increase a bit size in tokens if you're
talking again about entropic models,
but for most of the cases it will reduce.
So basically there is blacklisted fields
like this.
Which usually we don't need.
So kind of descriptions like information
about creators,
URLs which I never use in in in in my
agents etcetera.
So it's kind of blacklisted.
So if I use it.
Let's see. Go back.
We have a ticket and then I just what I'm
doing. I'm just using ticket to text.
We will not get this number,
but our goal here to get something less
than this one.
Let me run it.
OK.
Probably I need to do some printing
better here, but yes, this one.
OK, almost same as raw data a bit more.
Why?
Let me just show you in debug if I just
do debug here.
So we have a ticket like Jason's Jason's
structure after transformation.
We have it.
1.
Like this.
So we we have next we we are saying like
will be fields the key then will be like
it's kind of like structure.
I have full description of this
transformation so probably you can use it,
probably you can replicate in other
languages.
And this how what we are getting about
the ticket.
So this structure can be converted back
to the Jason but I never did it but it it
should be kind of backwards compatible
and so like at the end we have a key.
So this description there is some summary
so like.
And it's automatically transformed so.
Why I'm showing it?
So here one object if we have.
Errays.
It will be again transformed in the way
that if it's simple array you will not
have kind of keys for each object inside
of array.
It will be keys at the top and then will
be enumeration of the objects below.
So let me show you example,
but by the way it's not really cool
example for the session,
but let me show you if you have teams
client.
I want to get chat messages.
For for current chat AI dot M I'm
specifying 0. OK, not this one row this.
So in chat messages and let me kill it.
Just put it like OK.
Let's stop it.
Play.
OK,
I'm not the top guy in the English
Remove file.
language. OK, let's do this.
Let me just stop it. What you will see.
So this limit 0 means that I will
download all messages.
What do you mean will?
What do you think will be next?
OK, so you still here or?
We have here.
Yes.
OK,
so we have currently 385 messages in our
We are sinking.
chat. How's it looks like?
Pavel, welcome over, Pavel.
Yeah.
No.
Sorry.
OK, let me just.
Don't stink.
How's that area looks like if you're
talking to teams?
You so I did develop this like CLA tool
for Microsoft Teams reading messages
personal for me. Yeah so we have a chat,
you see the structure like summary,
blah blah blah,
some other part body body it's HTML even
from there is information about people.
Some IDs, etc.
So this is our chat history.
What will be next?
So if I attend it to all of them,
what do you think?
Probably it will try to summarize in in
five sentences what you requested.
OK. Any other?
Context might be exceeded.
OK, cool. Anything else?
No hallucinations. OK,
so second speaker was right,
Hallucinations.
but again I I did try it before.
So you see that.
Let me stop it because there is Infinite,
not Infinite, but we'll better try logic.
Yes. So we have.
Error as that where it was. Yes,
input is too long for the model.
So basically with current approach it's
kind of just 385 messages and model.
Already cannot do with this anything.
Where is the the like did we write in 212
weeks like a big book already?
Something I did miss probably.
Yeah so something strange because we did
hear a news like you can send money books
like a.
Context and get some summaries,
whatever else, right?
That does not work in this scenario.
Let's just try the simple approach like
with LM optimizer. To be honest,
I don't know, will it work or not? Yes,
let's see. I will run it.
So he.
But I I believe that there have to be a
method like a name role the the line #75.
So you requested the rough data.
So I believe there have to be a method
like give me just the messages without
the additional details,
additional parameters.
So maybe it will be working.
the same way as you are trying right now.
Yeah, so like even you see,
so input length still is big.
So we have 200 tokens,
200K tokens as an input and 64 I want for
output.
Which is more for than for limit for this
model.
Even you see this is simplified already,
but still there is a garbage which we
don't want. That's why like we have it.
I did market like MCP teams message role.
Yeah so like.
You can get it like plain Jason.
If models or people want to play with
these, that's fine.
But overall basic method for teams
messages will be simplified which return
like this.
Outers, bodies, dates, reactions,
mentions, attachments,
attachments which is like kind of URLs,
but let me show you.
So the same logic chat messages,
chat chat messages.
OK, it's a string.
You see I even did not use it with Java
because if I would use it with Java so
then then I would have it like an object.
So it's designed for LLM for the agents.
So for the agents I don't see sense
sometimes to do some transformation
string to objects if I do have Jason so I
just to have a string.
So we have this message.
I will remove this one.
Just to show you.
And run.
So you see that it download same
basically data 350 something messages and
there is you can see already what we have
date message type event like because it
was basic part.
So OK so it's done now and you see.
Sergei Makariev said like about something
blah blah blah and you see this is human
friendly, not only LLM friendly,
but also human friendly.
So and you can read it as a chat.
And you see that our LLM also did read it.
We have 5 sentences 12345.
And it's it's correct.
So the same content basically,
but provided in different manners. Yeah,
so and that's something what you need to
understand when because when you write in
SDLC agents,
you need to understand what is behind of
it because there is no magic.
How? How to simplify it more?
Just like just write name,
date without keys. Yeah,
so like like this.
Do not write keys at all, just write. OK,
it's a system messages.
I did keep it like it is.
For processing recordings etcetera.
But for instance you can remove date
outer reactions body and just play to
place date, name,
reactions and body and then you will
reduce more the tokens,
so even less than it's used now.
So by the way how many of tokens we did
it?
It's also interesting.
45 K so that means I can even send.
The 700 messages at once. Yes,
quality probably will be less at some
point,
but if I I'm asking overall questions or
summaries or direct one like so that
still will work and will work properly.
And you will get much less gallutinations
with this approach.
If you're preparing the context text,
let's say in the correct manner,
you will get better quality,
less gallutinations because.
For different models like these brackets,
quotes and so this kind of Jason words
etc. Keys I mean it can.
Producing hallucinations for you as well.
Yeah,
so like this is important to understand.
Think what is behind of it.
And if you're developing the tools for
for for others, also think about it.
So we can do experiments. There is 45K.
In the case my tool doesn't work properly,
I mean transformation.
Because let's just try it.
Because I already simplified this a lot,
let's say at the beginning and the
problem with my tool is that currently in
Jason I don't write the key if there is
no value.
But in my tool, I will write a kind of.
This character which will be considered
as one token. So that's why if I run it,
let me just show you,
it will be a bit more tokens than 45 K
should be.
So you see now that it is transformed via
my tool.
So we we we still have these blocks and
we have many.
Many empty spaces.
This is how how it is designed format.
If if there is like we have the keys
which is collected at the top then we
have area like 01234 but if there is no
value it will be empty so but still it it
it will be in this body and this space is
also.
By entropic consider it as tokens,
so that's why if we check now tokens,
it will be more than 45, yes.
Lexis.
But if you, for instance,
change it to to Germany Flash.
It should be less because Gemini should
not count spaces, but I don't know.
Let's see.
Oh,
do we have the same context window for
all the models?
No,
it's I I have the page somewhere I can
find it.
It it's a thing for for Gemini it will be
kind of 1,000,000 for Entropic Cloud 3.
7 in 200. It's 200 KK. Yes, 200 K tokens.
200K.
So let's see here.
Yes, it's from tokens. Oh, even again,
45 key. Interesting to be honest.
But let's see.
In the case you see,
it's even more than four entropic,
which is interesting. Let's remove it.
Why am I I just show it? For instance,
I need to process 5550 test cases 50.
I'm preparing them in the right way.
I just don't send the full array to LLM
for processing.
I'm transforming it to text specific
which is really simplified way.
So that's why I can really process 10K
like we are processing about.
How many OK in the biggest filter I think
5 of 5K test cases.
We are processing it in 7 minutes,
sometimes in 10 and we in in like we for
for each new test cases creation we do
this.
But during the year we spent only 66K
dollars. Yeah, so like and it's nothing.
So if you work with context properly,
so then you save money at the end.
And get better quality.
It's also important.
Let's see without OK from tokens.
It's still less.
Vladimir,
does this mean that in some cases we
could use different models for extracting
information from MCPC server using less
tokens and then use another model to
process the results?
To get better output.
I would not suggest to do this.
Uh, because um.
If you have structured content from MCP
like I did show here so chat messages row
Mhm.
and chat messages here you should write
script.
Why spend tokens for this work at all?
Because just to give you example,
you you can write you have an agent in in
cursor. Let me just show you.
You mean we shouldn't use MCP server,
we should use scripts to extract this
Yeah, something like this.
So if you if you're talking about agents
similar data without usage.
development and the topic really about it,
let me show you here.
I think it's connected, yes.
So for example, I can write here.
Something like give me JQL or search for
I don't know.
Ms. teams related tickets in JIRA.
So in this case first we call it tokens
to write a function.
Let's say to call MCP, then we call MCP.
It's also it's kind of like again tokens
then we get them back then.
It processes it and it processes this
like raw Jason, etc.
So if you know that you need to do all of
the same thing for your agent,
it's better just automate it.
That's what I want to say at the
beginning.
For instance,
if I'm writing the user story all the
time, in this case what I need,
you see that it finds everything. Yeah,
so OK, something killed guys,
are you here?
Mm-hmm. Yes.
OK, so it it was not, it was not teams.
OK, it was cursor. Let me open it.
Yes.
So.
Again, for instance, let's go go to Jira.
Let's think now about process.
I want to design this ticket.
SDLC I do create ticket right?
So if we are moving to LM's.
Give me details about the ticket.
And most of the agents feature,
let's say low code, yeah,
so they will do the same.
So you see the Jira get ticket is that it
run with I think default parameters,
default parameters what I'm.
What I mean in the case it is like this,
so it will take summary, status,
attachments, so something what is.
According to my experience to work
several years, around 10 to be honest.
So when I did work with Jira,
I I do have least most of the fields
which are common for most of the projects
and you don't need usually more than this.
If you need more,
so then you use custom fields.
It's also possible, yeah.
So here you see basic information,
blah blah blah.
So we get this information about ticket
here, right?
So and we spent already tokens.
O first we did use tokens when LLM
understand understands that we need to
call MCP this one.
So then with this MCP it generate request
like OK with methods of these will be
suitable for the task.
There should be somewhere Jira get ticket
I think.
I think this one yes basically gives me
the ticket by by ID. Yeah so.
What it does,
it does basically the same what we just
did with you.
Tracker perform this one TP 795 but with
default value like like this one get
default query fields.
Then it gets information.
So you spend tokens here,
then you spend tokens to process the
Jason what you got from the JIRA already
twice.
That exactly what what is done by many
agents what we now can design in
different tools.
The easiest one example I think called me
right so or or even cursor so I can make
instruction like for instance if I want
to describe the ticket summary then you
need I I will give you a ticket XYZ then
you need to call this MCP.
To get the ticket details and then you
need to use for instance.
Let me show you again template.
Yes, this one.
For example you need to use template like
this to describe it and all time when you
will call the agent it will ask tools,
it will download the data,
it will process the data,
it will ask another tool again.
To the load the data to process the data,
but all these context preparation part it
is nothing about LLMS.
It is script.
So.
That's why when we call.
Agent like AI teammate like business
analyst.
We are moving mostly to this part.
I hope we will have enough time.
There is design for me like teammate.
So it's it's just job.
So we we which has a lot of parameters,
not not not so many to be honest,
but like hooks, CLA commands,
AI processing,
there is some jobs params with what we
have like input JQL initiator.
Some metadata operations, blah blah blah.
So something what is really for the
script, not for LLM.
Something what we are doing all the time.
We are getting the ticket,
we are parsing these.
If there is Figma URLs,
we need to go to Figma if there is.
Confluence URL.
We need to go to Confluence.
In some cases we need to read comments,
in some cases we need to get attachments,
etcetera. Yeah,
so this this part it is automated so.
We have initiator, we have input query,
we have field name which is output source.
There is source processing.
It's like when Vanya Trifonov said like
Volvo designed MCP before MTCP,
he means this part. So because like.
I really like have kind of Uri to object
interfaces to different tools which I'm
supporting which are converting kind of
ticket to context or confluence URL to
the context.
If it has something behind of it,
like sub pages, sub tickets,
parents and whatever else or subtasks,
again it will process it like script,
not like a model.
So then we have also AI role.
Instructions, formatting rules, few shots,
blah blah blah which can be hosted
somewhere.
And then we have context orchestrator
which first of all goes to the
instructions and if there is confluence
URLs, if there is.
JIRA tickets or GitHub files reference.
It will download it and put it to the
context extract it.
I hope you see the difference.
So we are not calling model to make the
decisions because we know that it must be
done and we are using script algorithm
programming languages to develop this
part.
That's why like I did write my tools like
you you probably will have your tools
because it's you just need to call REST
API to get the JIRA description which is
one method.
So where you need to download talk
attachments, it's another method.
You need to go to Confluence.
It's sort method, yes.
So then three methods you need to go to
Figma. OK,
44 methods you need to wipe code develop
to prepare the context.
Without LLM then when it's done.
So in my case I'm using JQL.
So what we're doing like search and
perform. Yeah.
So in this case what we're doing we just
get in. OK, it's already long one.
So we just go in with JQL which is input.
Usually it's one ticket.
Because like it's designed like this,
but we can do this in in the if you use
in polling model.
I mean when you have hosted on on Jenkins
or GitLab or GitHub,
not sure to be honest about scheduling of
jobs but.
Then you can ping some JQL and all the
tickets which will be in JQL will be with
this logic.
So here what we have we have you can skip
it for now.
You don't need it like kind of like
JavaScript preprocessing logics and kind
of post processing.
Here you see that I'm collecting context,
so with comments.
But I do not extract extra tickets here
in this part.
So what I'm doing like OK ticket context,
we are going to tracker client.
It's why it's tracker client because it's
really tracker client.
So it does not matter like let's say
which exactly tracker client you will use.
So currently I do support Jira.
I do support Rally because I did work
with Jira and Rally.
Jira is server and cloud Rally.
It's Rally client. Yeah,
so for instance if I want I can implement
this interface.
For GitHub and the same teammate will
work with GitHub but I never did it so
because I did not have reasons and yeah
then when Context Orchestrator prepare
everything we also making chunking of
this if needed and only after these and.
At the end when all contacts prepare it,
we do following two options.
We use Cursor Cloudcode Copilot.
Pardon me,
whatever else Li tools for orchestration,
then we are going to this part and we are
storing in input folder all this context,
Jira ticket, etcetera, etcetera, etcetera,
etcetera.
We can use even to put it like to one
prompt as well, just directly to to.
Go to call Claude,
code or cursor or whatever.
But in my case I I do use input because
first I did play with either,
then I did play with Gemini CLAI and
input did work for them,
but it also works for cursor pretty well.
So then we can go this direction if it's
specified or we are going to the
direction skip.
We are going to model itself.
If you are going to the model,
we have the generic request with all
params like.
Instructions like this one AI role,
instructions, questions, tasks,
blah blah blah blah blah blah and we are
going to our own agent which is Teammate.
Team OK, sorry. Team, Teammate, sorry.
Generic request this one,
which you see pretty simple.
Specify at role instructions.
Additional instructions if needed.
So blah blah blah.
That's strange even why I named this like
this and then also possible chunk
processing.
So what that means if the context which
we did collected before bigger than 100K
tokens or 200K tokens, it's configurable.
Then we will perform it in chunks and we
will kind of run agent several times and
then we will write final agent to to to
sum up the results and send it to Jira to
Confluence, GitHub, whatever else.
So this is how it's designed.
And with all technical details.
There is two options for you.
So easy way which I I will try to show
now in several minutes you you just use
my tools but you need to understand how
it works behind.
Or you should try to write something
similar.
And this is something similar is most
more important because then you will
really understand all the pain, let's say,
and all the logic behind of it.
So it's kind of your homework to decide
what you want to do so.
Because like this is really what we need.
I mean like what they want to share.
Not just like, OK guys,
we I I can set up for you a automate in 5
minutes. No,
that not something what I want to to to
share.
I want to share to your knowledge how.
This AI teammate is working behind the
scene. What is really inside of it?
Any questions before we move to fun part
with example?
Guys, I hope you hear me.
Yeah, yeah, we hear you.
Yeah, we do. Mhm.
Yeah, just no question.
Yeah.
Yogini.
No, no, just reacting.
OK, OK, all right.
So let's now come back to our story
description. Story description.
In my case, it's like a game,
this Timate agent,
which I just did explain how it works.
This is configuration for systemate.
So what is here role?
I think you understand it right?
Send instructions.
Template story.
The ticket will come in here.
So basically if it is specified from the
Jira,
it will this field will be overrided or
from any other input and also outer like
I mean initiator who did trigger it.
It's also me.
Let's say here by default is this number
you can find in profile in Jira is way or
like it's set set up in automation.
So basically if someone else will trigger
it, for instance era,
so it also will work.
What we have here instructions we.
Like first it's template,
just confluence page.
There is some text that agent needs to
write to response MD file.
There is some role blah blah blah
important points.
Use terminal CLAI.
For instance,
if agent needs to understand that the
image because not sure for today,
but week ago Corsor CLAI could not
understand the image file.
So that's why if even DM tools downloads
the attachment.
From the Jira ticket and put it to input
folder,
Corsor CL AI could not just use this
attachment and understand and understand
what exactly happens.
So that's why what I did,
I just did create Gemini AI chat like DM
tools MCP method and I specified to
Corsor.
That if Corsor needs to understand not
Corsor exactly,
but like overall statement that it needs
to use this request like data message
what you want and pass to the file.
Same about Figma.
So Corsor cannot read Figma and MCP on
CLEI. It's also challenging.
For now a week ago, not sure for now,
but a week ago it was challenging that it
did not work.
So again I also saying you cannot use MCP,
use just CLI comments.
So and there is we have DM tools.
Figma download image or file and there is
format set Figma URL blah blah blah et
cetera. So and then.
Sorry, sorry,
could you repeat this part please?
So inside the prompt instruction you are
telling to the model that they need to
use specifics MCP for getting.
Not MCP.
If if if MCP is available to configure in
runner environment,
then you can say exact MCP instructions
which should be used for instance.
Here I can create instruction for for
cursor like if user user is asking about
ticket use Jira.
Get ticket MCP method all time right?
I can do this or I can specify comment
like if we need to to to get JIRA ticket
because DM tool supports boss.
For all of this,
so I can just say Jira get ticket and OK
Mm-hmm.
let not show you when if it works,
but I hope the DMC 100 it should work.
So that does read environment variables
yes and you see the ticket here.
So basically if if you're this is hosted
version of DM tools which can be deployed
Mhm, OK.
and I use just like URL to MCP to
confluence to to Jira.
Etc.
This is local version of Dmtools which
you just install in one command.
I will show you so and then you can use
Dmtools with many other methods.
So basically like confluence like.
So easier to show it probably there is
some documentation.
Yeah so this command for installation
just one.
I tried to reuse cursor pattern for the
case.
So cursor also you can install with one
command.
So basically I did do the same for DM
tools.
Not sure if it works on Windows by the
way,
but but should for Mac OS it works and.
It doesn't work.
Does not work for windows.
Doesn't work. OK,
so probably someone can fix it, all right.
But interesting why it does not work.
We can discuss later you for for DM tools
it it requires Java 23 and it will be
less so not sure if it will work. OK,
let's come back.
So here we we are telling if something I
can do with CLAI agent.
I'm just creating DM tools method which
is available via terminal via NCP
depending on the use cases or boss and
then any CLA agent can use shell to call
it.
And then I get results, yeah.
So that's why for the use case download
Figma, Gemini.
And the things that's it.
So there is also some questions,
get existing questions you see.
So I'm just specified like use DM tools,
Jira search by JQL and there is a JQL
like parent ticket XYZ, yeah.
So then I understand this so like OK if
request is about it so then we use it.
Then also important point here is this
one.
This is account ID of your AI team mate
like my AI team mate which I created and
registered in Jira. So this is reaction.
On the tagging.
So for the use cases when you have
already full description but you just
need to correct something,
you need to just prepare the table with
translations or do something else what
was not done before, so then.
It looks for these patterns and then
react just only on this part. Then yeah,
these just instructions because by some
reason that it write all the time this
one then reference to format Jira
markdown just.
All the time tell to LLM which markdown
we do use because markdown,
it's not the same like Jira markdown,
yeah?
So that's why it's important to specify
and I have this page which is used and
then just calling of this LA agent.
This one in my case Cursor you can why
it's script because some time ago even
Cursor did not work properly with so it
just freezed on runners but now it works.
So I put model here Sonnet 4.
5 because at some point also I did use
model 4 and.
It was updated and it's gone.
So that's why I decided to have small
wrapper on the cursor on top to have
capabilities just to put something in one
place. Yeah,
and there is workaround for freezing of
cursor. Now I did remove it because.
Because they do have an installation
already kind of redirection for different
environments.
So the problem was that version which we
did install on GitHub runners for Linux
that did not work properly,
but that was designed I think for Mac OS.
So now they do have separation for Linux,
for Mac, etcetera.
So it it is visible when Corsora is
installing.
Probably that's why DM tools does not
work on Windows because I am working on
Mac.
Then field I want to have it in
description operation time replace a
replace.
Means full description will be replaced
with output from the model.
There is also possibilities happened like
just add on top of what is already there.
There is possibility for debugging just
to get output of response as a file.
Why do have it?
Because when I just did experiment with
all of it,
sometimes responses from LLM were too big
because people did ask crazy questions
about code bases and that's why like if
it's not possible to put it to
description,
we just could attach it as a file and
people did read it.
Yeah,
so in the case because we use cursor for
processing,
we disable teammate processing and after
it we execute JavaScript function which
is just assigned for review.
Method from from this one.
This JavaScript it's running via Java
bridge so it is Graal JS engine inside of
it which I'm running via Java.
So there is some capabilities like to all
my MCP tools like Jira.
And to take it move like this one.
So basically when when we have
description from AI what we are doing we
are signing ticket back to initiator.
Again it is a code.
Not instructions in your agents,
but it is a code, right?
So people ask LLM saying LLM is
glucinating when I'm asking it to
download the ticket to do some work to to
to to write descriptions,
then assign ticket back to me,
blah blah blah blah blah blah.
If you know pre instructions,
post instructions,
which are usually the same,
just write it in the code.
You don't need LLM for this work.
Why you need to call ask LM to to use
tools to search for the tools to write
these tools on the on the fly.
If you can just write it in the code like
this.
Like assign ticket, move to status,
add label.
That's it.
Overall,
why I'm saying and I can set up for you a
automate in 5 minutes because if you're
going to the point I have this yes and
not not this one. Let me find.
Um.
By the way,
I did preparate for event in Minsk. Yes,
they have tools AI to me.
I did try it I think,
but I did like after this last month.
You see after this I did not use it.
So there is workflow description.
You can read it.
Uh, so there is instructions.
I can share it in the chat.
Let me.
We have the risk story description and
the story questions.
Same same same part as I just explained.
You see so then story questions also the
same then.
What is important to understand?
This is workflow.
So this is configuration for AITMA and
workflow itself looks like this.
So we just have configuration file.
To story description to story questions
for instance in the case not we are not
talking about development development you
can look to GM tools main main repository.
There is an agents say same approach
there is an agents like the resolution
design.
We can. I I want to talk about it later.
Yeah, Core description.
Let's me core description. Yes,
story development. I did name it.
No naming convention.
So there is instructions about
development here.
Also some capabilities what I still did
not merge because I have demo tomorrow
and they afraid to break something.
So like when this will support
instructions not only text one but also
like.
Passes.
So because we will have kind of files
with main instructions for for for most
of the scenarios then we can you know
like just play with this like formatting
rules, view shots etcetera.
Yeah also for actions here designed and
like this. So in short.
Here combination just your instructions
suggest array of references to the files
which you can use in configuration with
DM tools,
which you can use in configuration with
cursor.
For code code etcetera.
So and the idea that as mature or and
mature your project is becoming close to
AI agentic mode,
you you need to have more and more files
like this.
The problem for instance what I do see
even in Post ML because my team.
Has access to cursor,
but in repository I did not see any dot
cursor operations rules,
so probably they do have own. That's OK,
but still they did not apply it for the
repository.
That's something that I need to talk to
them and also.
We need to do something with this,
but you see that let's say all the text
just migrated to this part. Yeah,
so just files. It will be more fun,
but they did not match it yet.
So then encoded config permissions and
then what we are doing. OK,
Ubuntu by the way, if you use Mac OS here.
The run is faster so but overall we set
up Java.
You can clone this repository and you
will have the same then cache for it.
Installing cursor is basically one
command.
Like this,
but there is just checks that it's
installed.
Then install MDM tools again one comment
like this.
Then we again just checking that
everything is correct and the cursor API
model models does not make sense.
I think in the case even that will not
work probably.
Yeah,
probably that will not work because it's
months ago, but let's see. And then.
Not sure if you have this Sr.
script here CICD. Yes we have.
Yeah it will break you see.
So like some time ago I did write it and
it is that it use Sonet 4 but we can fix
it now.
So and then what what what happens?
We have all the secrets what I did ask
you to do last time Cursor API,
Jira e-mail, Jira API token.
Confluence if you want,
but usually the same for for the Jira
Gemini API to read images.
So DM tools integrations like Jira,
Confluence,
Figma and AI and we are specifying what
is available just to again reduce the
number.
And then what we have encoded config here
and config file there.
Let's go to automations.
Uh, OK.
Let me probably copy this.
How I can do this? By the way,
the automations I also wanted to automate,
but unfortunately it's available only via
internal Jira API,
so it's possible to automate creation of
automations.
Only in the way if you use some
extensions in browsers or some.
Yeah,
basically some JavaScript injections.
Let's make a copy. Copy of the item.
Let's name it like 2.
There is usually you have configuration.
When you owner of Jira you use global
scope.
If you have lead permissions you will
have project scope in my case usually.
In post ML I use just only project scope
and I set up that private rule because
nobody should be able to manage it except
of Maine. So then.
When rule will be triggered.
In the case you see we specify this
condition if assignee is teammate and
ticket is in status analysis or backlog.
This is a trigger which we just use.
I'm removing here this one.
I want just to have it. Yes, yeah,
now I need to clean up it.
OK.
Work item signed.
No rule details how to do this.
OK, let me go back better. Let me.
Just create a rule from scratch.
Um.
For example,
if you don't have service account like AI,
you cannot make trigger when ticket
assigned to AI,
then you have manual trigger and you can
specify who will be able to do this.
For instance,
we want to have this automation only for
story and then we even.
Can ask something to prompt here and then
we can set up same like BA and I think
this manual trigger yes story.
That company then we can create variable
with token.
That works like this variable GitHub
token.
And then you specify the token.
Like this,
it's personal access token to trigger
automation.
Then next we need to send request.
In our case it is send web.
We are specifying URL,
so you see there is Eastern DM tools,
actions, workflow, blah blah blah.
Let me go to this one and copy this past.
It's.
We want to call another workflow to see
that it will not work,
but then I will fix it.
I'm just replacing the path to another
repository.
So in your case it will be your for for
GitLab you will have another.
URL and probably another URL for body.
Yeah so not probably but definitely.
So then we we are saying it will be post
request and here we use just custom date.
I'm specifying that I'm using main branch.
I'm telling that I'm going to use this
configuration file story description
which is hosted here.
Then we have encoded config. Why encoded?
Because you cannot send really long text
and all other stuff to to GitHub
workflows as parameters and I assume for
GitLab as well so.
You have this config and uh,
this config will be.
Paused here.
So the tools run config file which is
story description and encoded config and
this encoded config.
Contains.
Params for our agent to overwrite.
So basically ticket description where we
did click a button or which we did assign
to a automate and initiator.
So me in the case.
O.
And that's it.
There is also headers which are required
for GitHub like accept.
Except which is.
I don't remember what is here.
Yeah, it's like VND application, VND,
GitHub,
V3 plus Jason and then also authorization.
Who is the talk?
In enterprises you you can have secrets
in Jira where you can store the tokens.
This token usually should be only read
only, need to be read only.
Because that can be used only for trigger
automations.
If you're owner of the JIRA or you manage
it like private automations,
only you who will see this.
But overall again be careful with this
part because it's only one thing which
can be.
So then there is another agent started
immediately to ask questions.
So first we are checking if labels.
Doesn't have AI questions asked.
So basically if you did not trigger the
agent before,
that's why I do have action JavaScript
and post action JavaScript because if I
do trigger action like for for for
writing questions and agent is working
before to start to work agent will
execute JavaScript.
We will mark it with label kind of like
I'm in progress or whatever.
Then if I trigger the same agent next
time it will check ticket.
I am working on this now.
Yes just break it like break the job and
do not continue. If not then continue.
Pretty in same manner we do ask we do to
send same same trigger but with another
agent workflow.
So that's why again let's try to it's
manually trigger it. OK,
GitHub is not here.
Let me stop sharing try to put.
Token.
Uh.
OK, turn on this.
OK.
And.
Back to sharing.
Yes, we have 5 minutes right now.
We have a ticket which is task. OK,
I don't have any types of bugs here.
Let's let's create something in GM tools
or or probably here.
I'm not sure.
So yeah, but basically it work type story.
If you have admin rights, it's so so cool.
Yeah, so. But if you don't have it,
then yeah,
it's it's a bit challenging story, some,
some, some test stories.
Then you need to be creative to really
make polling models,
injections like informations for
different.
Projects, etcetera.
Landing page for for webshop.
Online.
I don't know, for instance.
Let's create the story like an example.
So we have it. I I I hope you got it. Yes.
So that trigger can be assigned to AI to
mate or just clicking on the button.
This is another example because we did do
this automation.
You see AI to mate now like with a button.
And I because if I do assign it to the
automate will work another automation
which is using my IDM tools configuration
because I did set up it globally.
So here I'm clicking a button.
And let's see.
So that trigger if I go here actions.
We see that the trigger started.
We can look to this and it should fail on
cursor because there is Sonnet 4 model.
But I don't know.
I did not run it months for for for a
month. So you see what happens.
So it installs Corsort. Yeah,
they have pretty fresh version by the way.
Maybe it can read images.
We we don't know. Then it installs latest.
DM Tools 1760 already,
so not sure if it's latest one,
but we can double check. By the way,
today it did make new release with teams.
Yes, this latest one. So it's here then.
What it does, it fails.
So so even each each automation run it
will initiate the environment set up from
the scratch.
No, there is a cache rules.
If you configure it properly,
it will not download all the time cursor
or TM tools.
It will take it from scratch and Java set
up as well. I mean not not not scratch,
OK, it it won't be. Yeah, yeah,
I I got you.
but from the cache.
So it won't download the binaries itself,
but the installation process will be
Yeah.
remained.
Depending how do you use cache.
So basically you're describing the cache
Got it.
logic you can play with cursor.
So you have let me open the automate we
have.
Almost out of time,
but there should be cache. Yes,
you see that for Java I do use cache,
so Java installation will be cached.
Mhm.
Get it?
But overall for DM tools and cursor there
is no cache mechanism in the current
workflows.
So it will download all the time,
but it's pretty fast.
So because we hosted in a course or not,
but we host DM tools in in this workflow,
so that should work not workflow but in
GitHub releases.
So and you see that it's failed.
Mhm.
Um, now. Why? Because.
So we we have this encoded config,
yes and it's failed because it could not
run this CLI from from cursor.
Let me try to quickly.
Fix it.
If it will not work then tomorrow or not
tomorrow,
but later today I will just copy new new
version from.
Sonnet 4.5 this one.
M.
Probably, yes. OK, 4.
5 and there should be script.
OK.
Let me that script already outdated
because they did fix this freezing issue.
It is script should not be used anymore,
but let's try to check if it's not.
So I just need to copy paste from GM
tools and then it will work.
Let's come back to.
To this scenario and try to to rerun it.
Not sure by the way,
if he takes again from master main branch.
Usually for set up in post NL taking to
account the cache,
for set up it's 20 seconds.
To to restore the state from the cache.
Probably even we can speed up it more,
but don't really solve the sense of it.
No, something does not work. Let me,
let me.
Let's just finish it before closing the
call.
CICG scripts.
Let's try to see this.
Yeah, if it does not work,
then I need just manually copy paste.
And let's trigger this time from the
ticket again.
Vladimir,
do you really have this industrial grade
The.
noise around you indeed?
Uh, I'm sorry. Let me give me a second.
Why? Why are you still on?
Oh.
I'm working in underground and yeah,
so my kids,
they steal all rooms for for me.
I have 4 kids, hopefully they don't know.
So, and that's why, yeah,
I'm working in underground, let's say,
Wow.
and I have ventilation which is turned on
sometimes. Yeah,
that's where you hear noise.
But to be honest, like it's from laptop.
That's strange that Mike,
it's so cool to to to to to to to hear it.
OK, something is what I'm looking here.
With authorization,
so it prepares a context.
OK, I will fix it today,
but not for camera already,
just to save time for for for recording.
So a bit later today this workflow will
work. So I hope you got all.
Full end to end.
So basically the same thing I'm using for
DM tools,
the same thing we are using for Post NL
with a bit different setup.
So but overall the full chain I just did
show and also all details for what is
behind of it.
Homework,
homework to set up at least the workflow
with TM tools at least or.
You can set up it with Copilot CLI if you
have access to it without even DM tools,
just like it's kind of like more advanced
level.
So DM tools help you to kind of prepare
as a context, go to the Jira ticket,
download it and and all of the magic it
handled by DM tools.
But ideally for advanced, let's say level,
you should try to write everything by
yourself. Ideally without libraries.
I mean like you can use libraries as well,
but you.
You should understand what exactly you
send to LLM,
where exactly you prepare as a context,
how, how Corsor is taking your context,
how plot code is taking your context,
how copilot.
So and then like how do you read it from
LLM as well? Yeah,
how do you paste it to take it back?
This N to N thing it's ideally to have to
get full understanding of the process.
Yes, OK. If you have any questions,
so just write in the chat or ask me or
yeah, do this voice now as well.
Yeah.
So it'll be really useful if you could
again summarize very quickly the
prerequisites, right?
We need to install the cursor within our
VS code, for example,
whatever we have as the ID, right?
We do need to have Jira account,
preferably admin account.
It could be either in EPAM by the.
Some sort of request or?
You can create JIRA project yourself,
just register in Atlassian and create the
In.
JIRA and I did.
Uh huh.
So so any any version online cloud
version of Jira should should work.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
That's why I said like if you have two
accounts only, it will be even.
It will be free even with three accounts
or registered to the same general project
while you do not go to specific limits
Alright.
with automations.
Automations calls will be like will you
for free you have 100.
So then then next year it will be 1000.
So basically you can just go to Atlassian,
register your new JIRA project,
name it like my favorite JIRA project,
whatever else, or like your new startup,
I don't know.
And then try to integrate your project to
this agentic workflow. So this is a task.
I'm not asking you to use production
project with this, no,
because it requires restriction, approves,
etc. It's a lot you need to get.
Kind of like experience to play with cats.
Yes. So set up your own JIRA project.
You're working here.
You can do whatever you want. Yeah.
Register your Gmail account for AI
teammate.
Imagine that it's your personal worker,
let's say. Yeah.
And then try to repeat the same workflow
as I did with just this website and yeah,
hope answered.
And and from from from your experience is
it is it possible to have several Jira
item instances with the same e-mail?
Because I had my I I I'm I'm recovering
mine right now right?
I I had it abandoned some time ago.
Uh,
so probably it's one Jira account per
No, I don't know.
e-mail. OK, OK, couple of emails. OK,
mm-hmm.
One account per e-mail definitely,
but multi projects can be and multi URLs
for e-mail so.
OK, we'll investigate. We'll investigate.
Google it. Yeah, so if I did it,
so I think you can create your JIRA
whatever tools you you name it or your
startup name. Any other questions?
Yeah, but just like.
So Jira plus IDM plus plus code plus code
that should be sufficient for the starter
and then but but potentially personal
potential personal confidence or the
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So you.
confidence that comes with this personal
account will be sufficient.
Confluence will will be together with
Jira when you create it.
When I did create it for GM tools,
I got Jira URL and I got Confluence URL
Mhm, mhm.
as well. So and all access to the tools.
So that's why you can play with this as
Cool.
you wish and do not afraid to break
something. Yeah so.
That's the idea of the topic.
Mm-hmm.
And the life hack then if you create the
first first time account that never used
in Jira on any Atlassian products,
you will get actually first month premium
for free.
So you can use this one with full
capabilities.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
That's true as well.
And and and if you do not pay it then you
can get by the way for several days you
will get discount as well.
So it's also some tricks but will be
challenging to pay from Belarus location.
So I did use my Georgian.
Card for this, so it's also some issues.
They do block the block it,
but if you did pay from another location
so then you can use it from Belarus
without VPN as well.
So that's also interesting,
difficult to pay,
but if you already paid so then you can
use it.
So by the way, Corsor can be used. Yeah,
it's $2020.00 I think.
Or even like with free free limits you
can you can use it as well.
Sasha Sasha told me that probably Copilot
can be even cheaper. So Copilot chili,
but I did not.
So with Corsor CLA it works and I just
need to fix it for you.
But with Copilot CLA it should work but I
did not try it.
With entropic clot it will work if you by
some reason.
Have the license for entropic,
but again it just orchestrator.
You can even write it yourself.
All right.
OK. Thank you guys. Thank you.
Vova see you next week and then our in
our chat. Why?